Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing.
That surely someday we
just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
Uh, Luffy, take a good
long look at this lake.
Are you sure you want to cross it?
Uh-huh You gotta be kidding me!
It's going to be impossible
to get across that thing!
Half's on fire, the other half's frozen!
Then the temperature of the
water should be perfect.
Let's swim. You're crazy!
Robin and I can't get wet,
so you know what to do.
Are you trying to imply that
we should carry you across?
Actually, if we don't cross, we'll
have to go all the way around.
I've got no choice.
In that case, let me see what I can do.
Special attack, Green Star!
Grow, Fangrass!
Never seen this plant before.
Booty banana!
What? A boot!
This is awesome, Usopp!
We can use this Fangrass's oars.
You've got so many different seeds now.
How nice.
They're pretty handy, aren't they?
There were a bunch of crazy
plants in the Bowen Islands.
The deeper I went into
the dangerous areas,
the more useful the plants
I found along the way.
I survived there for two whole years.
There's no difficulty I
can't overcome! Nope! Not me!
Grandpa, get on board!
Or we'll leave you! Hey!
Just don't forget who supplied the boat!
All right, guys!
Let's take that away!
I want snow cones!
Why aren't you rowing?
Wow!
So breezy!
There's a strong headwind.
Of course.
It's the temperature difference here.
It creates a change in air
pressure, causing wind.
Look, the water's boiling.
You see, if we tried to swim across,
we'd have been poached pirates.
Can't you row any faster?
Why don't you try helping us, you bum?
You're not getting away.
Come back here!
Oh, crap!
Not that centaur again! Hey!
Let me guess, you changed your
mind and decided to join us?
Would you quit recruiting folks, Luffy?
Yeah, it's not like we need any more
strange creatures joining the crew.
A horn?
No, boss!
Boss?
That guy on the snail.
He said something about a boss, too.
Please, it's cold.
We need boss.
Finish off the intruders.
They're headed right for you.
Look at the shore on the other side.
Someone's there.
Where?
Guess that's the boss.
The distress signal was meant for him?
If that's the case, we don't
have anything to worry about.
This boss guy's got bigger problems
to deal with than us washing ashore.
There's a man among them
who's carrying swords.
Is he the samurai who attacked our people?
If so, I'll make him pay.
There's something creepy about this place.
It feels like we're being
watched by Akainu and Aokiji.
The thought gives me chills.
We should go back. Fire!
It's a river!
Way to go, Smokey! That was amazing!
I can't believe it!
How'd you know there was a
river behind that block of ice?
That was pretty impressive, Smokey!
It's like you got Saru
vision or something!
You can tell by looking at
the sea current, you morons.
You men need to start paying attention and
work on your attitudes while you're at it.
It is worrisome, sir.
That it is. Huh?
The fact that there was a hidden
river is not what's important.
In this situation,
what really matters is whether the ice
blocking it formed naturally or was man-made.
Hold up, Smokey.
You mean somebody might have been
hiding the river from us on purpose?
Come on, nobody lives here.
It's full of poisonous gas.
They'd have to be crazy to want to
live out their days in a gas mask.
The man on the snail definitely
mentioned the name of this island.
You probably just misheard him, Tashigi.
Not even a transponder
snail could survive here.
He's got a point.
If you've got time to laugh, you've
got time to break up more ice.
What in the hell is that?
Holy crap, it's a giant wall of ice!
Her warship is strong, but it's
no match for something that size.
What'll we do?
We've got to destroy it! Fire!
Wah-choo!
Okay, time to bust out of here!
Are you with me?
Let's go!
You're really fired up,
aren't you, Chopper?
You know it.
Sanji trusted me with
an important mission.
That means I gotta do my
best to protect the children.
I'll do whatever it takes
to get the job done.
Just watch me.
I'll get you out of here if
it's the last thing I do!
Watch out!
Don't be scared, kids.
I laugh in the face of
danger, because I'm a man!
Where do you think we should go from here?
I'm just security.
That's up to you, little lady.
Huh?
Miss, are you sure I'll be okay?
Oh, I'm positive.
You don't have to worry.
We're experts at getting
out of dangerous situations.
Just relax and follow us.
Watch out!
Now you made me mad!
Weapons, live!
Super!
He's got weapons all over his body.
Yeah, he must be the one who
broke the door open. Huh?
Sounds like you guys want
to get to know me better.
Okay, I'll spend as much
time here as you want, bro!
Load the poison gas canisters!
The kits are gone, the coast is clear!
All right, fire at will!
You should take off your masks, gentlemen.
Don't you want to smoke
poisonous gas with us?
Bastard!
Calm down, there's no reason to get angry.
He rips our masks off!
And he broke our air tanks!
Don't use gas canisters!
Whoa, what in the hell are you? Sheep?
Why you?
Just what are you doing down there?
Who on earth could this be?
This foe is different from
the others I've fought.
I've never been challenged like this.
They're quite the formidable opponent.
I got no clue what you're
talking about, bro.
Sorry.
My torso's currently in battle.
Say what?
What's going on?
I'm so confused.
Who are you and why are
you attacking me like this?
Where'd your head go?
And where are your legs?
How fretful!
I don't suppose you can speak.
Ready? Fire!
We're going to reach the
end of the river soon.
Really?
I wonder what we'll find there.
I've got a pretty good idea.
You wouldn't happen to be a
ghost bike, Chance, would you?
If so, you need to obey the rules.
You can't come out during the day?
Why are you attacking me?
I didn't do anything wrong.
The only reason I came ashore
was to make a snow army.
There's no point in fighting.
Why don't we build snowmen instead?
We can make snow sculptures if you like.
I don't understand how
he can attack with such
precision when he doesn't
even have any eyes?
No wait a minute!
I just remembered!
I don't have any eyes either.
He's strong! And... Stay
back!
I demand answers from you!
Can't you at least tell
me why you wish to fight?
You asked for it.
Hop-up-cour-droit!
Two-sword style?
Okay, now he's really
starting to scare me!
I can't handle it! He's so creepy!
And now somebody save me!
You called master yes did you capture the
escapees not yet but i
have news about g5 sir
Oh them i'm afraid the
poison gas didn't stop them
They've been firing their
cannons to break through the
ice flows They're slowly forcing
their way onto the island
It looks like they'll make their
way to the laboratory soon this is
quite vexing why do They want to
come ashore so badly do they know
something we don't tell me who is
their commanding Officer vice admiral
smoker oh is that so irksome but
not entirely unexpected i suppose
All right, then.
Conceal the ships we
have moored at the front.
Who's going to deal with them, sir?
No one is allowed to be on this island.
That means you cannot let them see you.
So you'll deal with them?
Don't be a fool.
I can't afford to reveal myself to them.
Then what do we do?
There's nobody else who can stop them.
You want me to handle it? Huh?
There's no gas here. What?
She's right.
I can't believe it.
I can breathe.
There was definitely poisonous gas
earlier, so where the hell did it go?
I assume it was released by
someone who doesn't want us here.
Whoa, who'd do that to us?
Wait, is this...
That's right. This is Dr.
Vegapunk's laboratory.
At least it used to be.
There shouldn't be anyone here!
It was abandoned a long time ago.
Think someone could be living here?
Come out and face us!
What's wrong are you
afraid of us or something?
No, we don't just have to stand here
ringing the bell waiting for him to answer.
No Uh,
all we really got to do is break down the
door with our cannon smoky that I mean mr.
Smoker, sir Anyone in there? Answer us!
Open this door or else...
Hey, listen up!
You're trespassing!
Nobody's allowed on this island!
I don't know who you are, but...
You're under arrest!
Come out right now!
Whoa, it opened!
Surrender at once, or we're coming for ya!
So tell me what brings you to my vacation
home white hunter oh man you gotta
be kidding me He used to be a rookie
with a 440 million berry bounty but now
he's among them dracula hawkeye Mihawk
the pirate empress boa hancock don
quixote do flamingo pirates backed by
the world government the Seven Warlords.
Hello, Trafalgar Law.
We should just go back
to the ship, Smoker.
I don't want anything to do
with him after what he did.
You heard about it, didn't you?
In order to become a member
of the Seven Warlords,
He delivered the hearts of a hundred
pirates to the Navy headquarters.
He's off the rails.
The guy's a creep.
You want to tell me
what you're doing here?
Surely you're aware that no one's
allowed to step foot in this island law.
Not pirates or government
allies. That clear?
Hmph, I see.
That means you aren't allowed either.
Mommy! Daddy!
Hey, what you said to me earlier,
about how you guys aren't sick anymore?
Yeah, what about it?
What was it like before?
I mean, like what kind of
disease did you guys have?
No clue.
All they told us is that
we were real sick and that
it would take us a whole
year to get well again,
so we had to come here and rest up.
I hear?
And they didn't tell you what was wrong?
Nuh-uh.
I guess maybe my parents found
out I was sick and asked the
people who work here to pick
me up and help me get better.
And that's how I ended up with this place.
That doesn't seem right.
Your parents really sent you away?
I was just playing outside one day and
those people showed up out of nowhere.
Then they brought me here
They said I had to go with
them right away or else my mom
and dad might get infected,
too
I didn't even get to say goodbye to them.
What about you guys?
Huh, this sounds like
straight-up kidnapping to me
So a bunch of strangers took
you to some weird place without
letting you say bye to your parents
That could only mean one thing.
You kids are really sick!
They were lied to, obviously!
You're not getting too tired, are you?
I can always carry you on my back.
We'll be okay.
Because the master takes really
good care of us. The master?
Yeah, he's so nice.
I'll get right on that.
Nami!
I got this!
So try this at home, kids!
You can thank me later.
He did it!
You're handy these days.
Yeah, good job, Mr. Raccoon.
I am not a raccoon!
Bet you do look like
one now. You're right!
Okay, we should hurry up.
Oh, it's cold!
Chopper, give me your fur!
That's your thing!
Hold on, no way!
Where are we?
Does this lead outside, or
is that some kind of freezer?
It's way too dark to see.
The temperature's perfect, if you ask me.
I can't see.
Oh, wait, look.
There's a door back there. Yeah.
Let's go see what's behind it.
No, stop!
It's scary!
We can't! Huh?
What's wrong? Let's go!
Come on, they'll catch us!
Yes, but I can't, because that's the
way they brought me in when I came here.
Really?
Great, that means it must be an exit then.
I know it's cold, but
you can make it. Come on!
No, it's not that.
It's, um...
Look around. Huh?
What?
It looks like there's
something inside the wall.
See?
It's scary because the
walls are full of people.
Are those corpses?
Encased in walls of ice?
And the ceiling? Look!
The floor, too!
You're supposed to be the
bonob, so you don't leave us!
Hmm.
I hope that's enough.
You already blocked their way.
That's all we needed.
Let's go.
I swear I heard Nami screaming
her lungs out just now.
If she's professing her love
for me, then I have to be there.
Uh, anyway, who are those guys?
Half-man, half-sheep.
Isn't there some kind of creature
like that from a fairy tale?
Sorry, Franky,
but identifying fairy tale characters is
pretty far down my Daddy list right now.
I've got a damsel to save first!
Wait!
Unhand me, then! Leave me!
I did not see my son among
all the children we set free.
Perhaps there are more rooms here.
Allow me to stay and - And what?
You don't have any arms or legs!
If I leave you here alone, that means
it's my fault if anything bad happens.
I can't have that.
I care not.
My only goal now is to save my son.
You're on my last nerve.
All you have to say is
help me find my body.
We'll help you.
Swallow your pride.
Asking for help from you pirates?
I would rather die.
However, I suppose if you truly are that
desperate to locate the rest of my body,
I won't stop you from searching.
That's it!
I'm not taking any more lip from a head!
Well, if it's come to
this, I accept my fate!
At least I died with
my honor still intact!
Whoa, Sanji.
Destroying a helpless severed head
won't make you feel any better.
I mean, if you really
weren't taking his crap,
then you wouldn't have
brought him with us.
Ah, but...
Damn it!
This is driving me crazy!
I can't believe I was stupid enough
to be moved by his determination.
He's not strong.
He's just stubborn.
I don't want to help him Yes,
but I'm sure you must pity a poor
disembodied head who can't even
defend himself if someone attacks
So would you like to carry me,
pal?
Damn it as soon as you have an ass to
kick you best believe I'm gonna kick it
You show no mercy even to
those who can do you no harm.
You are a fearsome foe indeed pirate
Maybe Nami found a way out. Hurry!
That hurts. Itches.
Hello?
My name is Monkey D.
Luffy, and I'm going to
be king of the pirate.
You don't need to tell them all that!
Someone help!
What's wrong?
Please, it's cold!
We need boss!
Huh?
It's hot where we are.
My friends are getting cut
down, one after another.
The samurai is gonna kill us!
And where are you?
Please hurry, we're on
the island of Punk Hazard!
We don't have much time left!
He said cold, and named the island.
Given those facts,
it's almost undeniable that the signal
was sent from here on Punk Hazard.
And you've met Straw
Hat before, haven't you?
Gum-Gum!
Balloon!
Repel!
Now room and shambles.
You killed me!
Two years ago, during an incident involving
the Roswals, a celestial dragon family,
you, Luffy, and Kid fought together.
We know what happened at
the War of the Best, too.
Quick, hand over Straw Hat.
Hand him over and we can escape.
He'll die without my help.
Straw Hat escaped Aka 'inu's clutches.
And you helped him.
All right, then. What now?
I happen to know you Marines are
pretty good at faking those times.
distress signals.
If you're suggesting this is a trap
we set, I'm sorry to say you're wrong.
Is that so?
Well, sorry, I have no
more information for you.
You and I both know that's bullcrap.
Now I want to see what's inside that lab.
It's my vacation home, that's all.
So beat it.
You abandoned this place, so why can't a
pirate come to relax?
I don't see anybody else around.
And if Straw Hat does show I'll behead
him for you if there's nothing else?
Get lost!
You hear those voices?
Somebody's in there!
We're free now!
Whoa, it's freezing!
We've got it!
We're out of the building!
We're gonna be okay!
I get to see Mom and Dad!
It's cold now!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Franky!
Super duper tank's here to save the day!
Gonna squash that and find
it that gets him away!
Except for cute baby animals and stuff.
SUPER!
I'm Frank in the tank!
Woo! Now!
SUPER!
What exactly are we looking at here?
Giant kids, a raccoon,
a robot, a severed head,
and a lady who's not
dressed for the weather.
I don't know where to start.
That guy! I know him! Oh, yeah!
We saw him in Sabaody!
Are you the creep who
kidnapped those children?
You jerk.
They're kids.
What's wrong with you?
Why is he here?
Smoker, I'd recognize
that ugly mug anywhere.
And Tashigi looking good.
Wait a sec.
The Navy's here too?
Change of plans, kids.
We can't get out this way.
Look for another exit.
There should be a back door.
Try to find it.
Go on, hurry.
Will we bring the Navy
to a place like this?
Beats me! Let's just go!
But I always thought
the Navy were good guys.
Fine, go with them.
No, I don't want you.
They look kind of mean.
So you did lie.
There are others here.
Guess so.
But that was a shock for me, too.
Marines!
Track down the straw-hot pirates!
Aye, aye, Captain!
Come on, men, follow her!
Wait, stand back.
Room
Everybody all right?
Those fools bring trouble wherever they go
And tact
a battleship that's floating
in midair the river's
up there too what the
hell that makes no sense
i lied to you for your own good you should
have listened now that you've seen the
truth i'm afraid i can't let you leave
we're so screwed aren't we stay behind me
you're no match for law he'll
dismember you on the spot
KUKUSMORBIUS SHOWING THE G5 MEANS BUSINESS